<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Sergey Kotlov&#39;s blog where I write about my experience working at the international network of businesses called Happy Melly, helping people be happy at work and visiting inspiring organisations around the world which care about happiness of their employees.
</description>
    <link>http://changegeek.ru</link>
    <atom:link href="http://changegeek.ru/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Ministry</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/ministry.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Each company I visit has its unique atmosphere and dynamics. One reminds of a meetup where people learn new things, share experience and drink beer. Other reminds of a hackaton where participants press forward to create and deploy a working product as fast as possible. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ministry.de&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ministry&lt;/a&gt; is a family gathering where you are always welcomed, find support and be challenged at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/23/ministry.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/23/ministry.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working on the move. Survival guide.</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/survival.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Last ten weeks I enjoyed coffee in nine cities, visited sixteen companies, met five members of &lt;a href=&quot;http://happymelly.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Happy Melly&lt;/a&gt; team and had both very productive and very unproductive days.  I learned accordingly and created a list of rules which might help you to travel around Europe and work at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/11/working-on-the-move-survival-guide.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/11/working-on-the-move-survival-guide.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GoodGame Studios</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/goodgames_empire.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Working at organisations which grow very fast reminds me of bull riding. When several hundred people join a company’s campus during a year you should expect to change offices, switch projects and bump to a new person in your team every two weeks or so. These factors might decrease employees engagement. In addition, during fast growth management style tends to be more &lt;i&gt;command and control&lt;/i&gt; than &lt;i&gt;lead and adapt&lt;/i&gt;. It’s reasonable as many new people are not aligned with an organisation yet and couldn’t change direction fast enough all through self-organisation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/01/goodgame-studios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/06/01/goodgame-studios.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Netlight</title>
        
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;After reading a number of invitations I learned to predict if I would truly enjoy the time taking an interview and finding out interesting facts about an organisation. Probably the most important factor is a mood of a letter. You feel it with your fibres when an author sincerely loves the company, is proud of it and very excited to let everyone know more. &lt;a href=&quot;https://se.linkedin.com/in/karinhartzell&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Karin&lt;/a&gt; works at Netlight and her letter had all of those.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/05/03/netlight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/05/03/netlight.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yes before No</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/yes_no.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Several days ago Jurgen wrote a very nice post about purpose and commitment, &lt;a href=&quot;http://noop.nl/2015/04/no.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;No&lt;/a&gt;. If you haven’t seen it yet, &lt;a href=&quot;http://noop.nl/2015/04/no.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;check the article&lt;/a&gt; right now. It’s important for understanding the text below. I wait while you’re reading.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/28/yes-before-no.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/28/yes-before-no.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve never been bored in 15 years</title>
        
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I promised myself to write this post yesterday. I actually started it. And then I opened Crisp’s blog and got sucked into it. It’s that good. I haven’t visited it for a while and spent at least an hour enjoying the articles. I recommend you to do the same. Right after you finish this post :)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/24/crisp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/24/crisp.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AgilePeople</title>
        
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the goals of my tour is to meet people from &lt;a href=&quot;http://happymelly.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Happy Melly&lt;/a&gt; network. I was more than lucky in Helsinki to spend a day with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/skotlov/posts/10202842788510087&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Marja and Hannu&lt;/a&gt;, and to have a couple of beers with &lt;a href=&quot;/blog/2015/04/08/flowa.html&quot;&gt;Antti&lt;/a&gt;. What a good time it was! I couldn’t wait it would repeat some day in some way. Thankfully Happy Melly has its “agents” everywhere. Last Monday I finally met with Johan whom I haven’t seen for ages and Pia-Maria whom I’ve never seen in person.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/21/agilepeople.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/21/agilepeople.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Vincity</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/vincit.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;My arrival to Tampere wasn’t welcoming. It was snowing, windy and quite cold. I realized that I made a mistake leaving my gloves at home. Morning city didn’t make a slightest attempt to improve the situation. WiFi in the cafe I chose because of the sign “Free WiFi” was broken. Three random commuters I asked about the nearest coffee shop couldn’t help me. Nevertheless I didn’t allow those small troubles to spoil my mood and I was right. Several hours in Vincit are worth much more “suffering” than I got.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/17/welcome-to-vincity.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/17/welcome-to-vincity.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FutuFriday</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/futurice_1.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://futurice.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Futurice&lt;/a&gt; and me have the longest “relationships” among the organisations in my tour. It sparkled my interest in more detailed investigation of fantastic companies. Futurice also became the first organisation which I studied carefully and wrote a &lt;a href=&quot;/research/futurice.html&quot;&gt;case study&lt;/a&gt;. As you see it was no surprise at all I was excited when &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ykarikos&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yrjö&lt;/a&gt; invited me to take part in &lt;em&gt;FutuFriday&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/16/futufriday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/16/futufriday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reaktor</title>
        
        
          <img src="http://changegeek.ru/images/reaktor.jpg"/>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://reaktor.fi&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reaktor&lt;/a&gt; got into my sight when I was preparing for two weeks in Helsinki. I went through my notes and found the only brief &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/finnish-reaktor-innovations-was-selected-as-the-best-workplace-in-europe-152597585.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; about the company. It described that Reaktor won Best Place to Work in Europe award two times. Nevertheless, I got hooked. My interest grew considerably after I had visited their website and watched the video below. Reaktor’s own band recorded it and they use it “to make recruiting the summer help a whole lot more fun”.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/14/reaktor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changegeek.ru/blog/2015/04/14/reaktor.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>